In the last lesson we talked about tenses basically how we change verbs in time and that's very important.
在上一课中，我们基本上讨论了时态如何及时改变动词，这非常重要。
That's really important to understand but we also need to begin to use English in real situations.
理解这一点非常重要，但我们也需要开始在实际情况中使用英语。
We need to be able to apply it to things we need to do in real life.
我们需要能够将其应用于我们在现实生活中需要做的事情。
So in this lesson we're going to talk about how to invite people to do something.
因此，在本课中，我们将讨论如何邀请人们做某事。
We're going to go through lots of examples and we're going to frame this around a phone call because
我们将通过很多示例，我们将围绕电话进行框架，因为
that just helps us make it pretty simple.
这只是帮助我们使它变得非常简单。
We're gonna do it as a single phone call.
我们将通过一个电话来完成。
One friend inviting another friend to go out to eat.
一位朋友邀请另一位朋友出去吃饭。
That will be basically our situation and we're gonna go through lots of words and phrases and the steps
这基本上就是我们的情况，我们将经历很多单词和短语以及步骤
of the call how it usually happens basically the things we learn in this lesson I want to be very clear
电话通常是如何发生的 基本上我们在这节课中学到的东西
can be used in lots of other situations.
可以在很多其他情况下使用。
And just because we learn something doesn't mean that's the only way this can be done.
仅仅因为我们学到了一些东西并不意味着这是可以做到的唯一方法。
There are many ways to invite.
邀请方式有很多种。
There are many phrases that we will not learn today that you can use which are also correct.
有许多我们今天不会学习的短语，你可以使用它们也是正确的。
So I just want to be clear about that first.
所以我只想先明确这一点。
OK now I also understand that nowadays most people invite other people on you know Facebook Messenger
好的，现在我也明白了，现在大多数人邀请其他人在你知道 Facebook Messenger
or whatever app you use.
或您使用的任何应用程序。
Right.
正确的。
You don't actually call somebody on the phone very often and ask them to go somewhere with you.
你实际上并不经常打电话给某人并要求他们和你一起去某个地方。
Probably but it's still a basic skill and you can use the same thing in person and in fact you can use
可能，但它仍然是一项基本技能，您可以亲自使用相同的东西，实际上您可以使用
the same thing in a text message as well.
短信中也有同样的事情。
Maybe it's a little different but the basic ideas are the same.
也许它有点不同，但基本的想法是一样的。
We're gonna talk about how at the beginning of a call you need to have a small talk and then we'll go
我们将讨论如何在通话开始时进行简短的交谈，然后我们将继续
into making sure the person at the other end is actually available right now to talk to you and how
确保另一端的人现在实际上可以与您交谈以及如何
we actually handle that situation.
我们实际上处理了这种情况。
Then we actually ask the other person if they would like to do something we'll do it in a way that's
然后我们实际上问对方他们是否愿意做某事，我们会以一种方式去做
realistic not in a very fake way like I would like you to go with me or I would like to invite you to
现实不是以非常虚假的方式，比如我希望你和我一起去，或者我想邀请你
blah blah blah.
等等等等等等。
Actually not very common.
其实不是很常见。
Well we'll use some real natural words and phrases to invite someone to eat and then we'll talk about
好吧，我们会用一些真正自然的单词和短语来邀请某人吃饭，然后我们会谈论
how we can say no without being really rude and how we can say yes and show different levels of excitement
我们如何在不粗鲁的情况下说不，以及我们如何说是并表现出不同程度的兴奋
and then finally we'll talk about how we can talk about where we're going to eat and confirm where we're
最后我们将讨论如何谈论我们要去哪里吃饭并确认我们在哪里
going to go.
要去。